A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of Transportation, 2006-2010
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Constituent Correspondence, 2001-2005., Extent: 68 boxes. (Box 1-68)
  - Subseries B. Secretary's Correspondence, 2001-2005., Extent: 26 boxes. (Box 1-26)
    This subseries is housed in twenty-six archival boxes and is arranged in chronological order. The subseries contains correspondence from various constituents directly to Whittington W. Clement, and later Pierce R. Homer, as Secretary of Transportation. In addition, there is correspondence sent to Shirley J. Ybarra, Secretary of Transportation, between October and December 2001. The correspondence usually includes a copy of the Secretary of Transportation's letter in response. The correspondence in this series relates to the following topics: the Outer Connector - Northwest Quadrant, Interstate 81, the Virginia Birding & Wildlife Trail, Interstate 73, Route 29 Charlottesville Bypass, the "Techway" Bridge, Route 37 eastern Extension, Route 340, National Capital Region, the Northern Virginia sales referendum, Route 221, traffic signal timing & synchronization, Aviation World's Fair, the Public-Private Transportation Act, the Dulles Rail Public-Private Transportation Act Advisory Panel, Special Task Force on Truck Safety, Humelsine Parkway, Department of Motor Vehicles, Western Transportation Corridor, Highway Marker Program, Amtrak, drunk driving, Six-Year Improvement Program, HOV lanes, Hurricane Isabel, Commonwealth Transportation Board (CTB), Federal Surface Transportation Program, Virginia Capital Trail, Highway Sign Program, Roadside Management Program, VTRANS 2005, the Jamestown-Scotland Ferry, Dulles Toll Road, red light enforcement, Dulles Corridor Metrorail Project, the Statewide Transportation Improvement Program, high occupancy toll lanes on I-395/95 Corridor, and the Tri-County Parkway.
    - 2001
      - October (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - November (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - December (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - 2002
      - January
        - 2-25 (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - 28-31 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - February
        - 1-18 (Box 46, Folder 6)
        - 20-28 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - March
        - 1-13 (Box 46, Folder 8)
        - 18-28 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - April
        - 2-5 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - 8-16 (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - 17-29 (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - 29-30 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - May
        - 1-15 (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - 16-30 (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - 31 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - June
        - 3-12 (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - 13-24 (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - 25-28 (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - 28 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - July
        - 1-18 (Box 48, Folder 7)
        - 22-24 (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - 25-31 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - August
        - 1-9 (Box 49, Folder 3)
        - 12-21 (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - 22-31 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - September
        - 3-13 (Box 49, Folder 6)
        - 17-20 (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - 23-30 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - October
        - 1-7 (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - 7-8 (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - 9-18 (Box 50, Folder 5)
        - 21-23 (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - 24-30 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - November
        - 1-7 (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - 8-20 (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - 21-27 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - December
        - 3-6 (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - 9-17 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - 18-23 (Box 51, Folder 6)
        - 26-31 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - DMV Complaints, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Other Referrals, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Requests for State Aircraft, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Road Problem E-Mails, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - 2003
      - January
        - 2-23 (Box 52, Folder 5)
        - 28 (Box 52, Folder 6)
        - 29-30 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - February
        - 2-19 (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - 20-28 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - March
        - 3-12 (Box 53, Folder 3)
        - 13-31 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - April
        - 1-14 (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - 15-25 (Box 53, Folder 6)
        - 28-30 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - May
        - 1-7 (Box 54, Folder 1)
        - 8-22 (Box 54, Folder 2)
        - 23-30 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - June
        - 2-4 (Box 54, Folder 4)
        - 5-11 (Box 54, Folder 5)
        - 12-13 (Box 54, Folder 6)
        - 16-20 (Box 54, Folder 7)
        - 23-30 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - July
        - 1-7 (Box 55, Folder 2)
        - 8-14 (Box 55, Folder 3)
        - 15-25 (Box 55, Folder 4)
        - 28-31 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - August
        - 4-14 (Box 55, Folder 6)
        - 8-22 (Box 55, Folder 7)
        - 25-29 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - September
        - 2-8 (Box 56, Folder 2)
        - 9-19 (Box 56, Folder 3)
        - 22-30 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - October
        - 1-10 (Box 56, Folder 5)
        - 11-27 (Box 56, Folder 6)
        - 28-29 (Box 56, Folder 7)
        - 30-31 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - November
        - 3-13 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - 14-18 (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - 19-26 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - December
        - 1-10 (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - 11-18 (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - 19-31 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - DMV Complaints, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Requests for State Aircraft, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - VDOT Complaints, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - 2004
      - January
        - 5-8 (Box 58, Folder 4)
        - 9-21 (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - 22-31 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - February
        - 1-13 (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - 16-27 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - March
        - 1-10 (Box 59, Folder 3)
        - 11-24 (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - 25-31 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - April
        - 1-15 (Box 59, Folder 6)
        - 16-23 (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - 26-28 (Box 60, Folder 2)
        - 29-30 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - May
        - 3-4 (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - 5-19 (Box 60, Folder 5)
        - 20-27 (Box 60, Folder 6)
        - 27-28 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - June
        - 1-4 (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - 6-15 (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - 15-18 (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - 21-28 (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - 28 (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - 29-30 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - July
        - 1-15 (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - 16-30 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - August
        - 1-8 (Box 62, Folder 3)
        - 9-19 (Box 62, Folder 4)
        - 20-31 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - September
        - 1-20 (Box 62, Folder 6)
        - 21-30 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - October
        - 1-12 (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - 13-26 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - 27-31 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - November
        - 1-10 (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - 11-30 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - December
        - 1-15 (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - 16-23 (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - 26-31 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - DMV Complaints, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Homer, Pierce R., 2004 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Other Referrals, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Requests for State Aircraft, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - VDOT Complaints, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - 2005
      - January
        - 3-11 (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - 12-24 (Box 64, Folder 9)
        - 25-31 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - February
        - 1-3 (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - 4-9 (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - 10-16 (Box 65, Folder 3)
        - 17-28 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - March
        - 1-12 (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - 14-23 (Box 65, Folder 6)
        - 24-31 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - April
        - 1-7 (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - 8-20 (Box 66, Folder 3)
        - 21-28 (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - 28 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - May
        - 2-3 (Box 66, Folder 6)
        - 4-17 (Box 66, Folder 7)
        - 18-24 (Box 67, Folder 1)
        - 25-31 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - June
        - 1-15 (Box 67, Folder 3)
        - 16-30 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Dulles Toll Road
        - June 3 (Folder 1) (Box 67, Folder 5)
        - June 3 (Folder 2) (Box 67, Folder 6)
        - June 3 (Folder 3) (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - June 3 (Folder 4) (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - June 3 (Folder 5) (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - June 3 (Folder 6) (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - June 3 (Folder 7) (Box 68, Folder 5)
        - June 3-16 (Folder 8) (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - July
        - 1-8 (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - 11-21 (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - 22-31 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - August
        - 1-10 (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - 11-19 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - 23-31 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - September
        - 1-12 (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - 13-14 (Box 70, Folder 2)
        - 15-29 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - October
        - 3-4 (Box 70, Folder 4)
        - 5-18 (Box 70, Folder 5)
        - 19-31 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - November
        - 1-8 (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - 9-16 (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - 17-30 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - December
        - 1-7 (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - 8-15 (Box 71, Folder 5)
        - 16-31 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C. FOIA Requests, 2002-2005., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1)
    This subseries is housed in one archival box and is arranged in chronological order. The subseries contains correspondence to the Secretary of Transportation by various constituents requesting information in accordance with the provisions of the Freedom of Information Act of Virginia. The majority of requests originate from Robert G. Marshall, delegate from the 13th District, and relate to construction projects listed in the Northern Virginia Sales Tax Referendum.
    - 2002
      - Marshall, Robert G.
        - 17 July-12 Sept. (Box 72, Folder 1)
        - 18 Sept.-7 Oct. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - 2003 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D. Trade Association Correspondence, 2002-2005., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1)
    - American Association of State Highway & Transportation Officials (AASHTO)
      - 2002-2004 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Southeastern Association of State Highway & Transportation Officials (SASHTO) (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Series III. Historically Significant Projects & Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1)
  The Historically Significant Projects & Files series is housed in one archival box and is arranged in alphabetical order. This series contains transportation files deemed historically significant. Includes are files related to Continuity of Operations Plans (COOP), Department of Conservation Resources - Lake Merriweather, presentations, Statewide Agencies Radio System program (STARS), Small, Women-Owed, & Minority-Owned Businesses (SWAM), and Virginia Information Technology Agency (VITA) Transition Plans.
  The Continuity of Operations Plans (COOP) file contains plans for the Port of Virginia and Virginia International Terminals to protect & preserve the continuing operations of the Port's activities and its economic benefit to the Commonwealth. The files also contain memorandums and certificates regarding the implementation of COOPs for disaster recovery, incident response, and occupant emergency response. Note that the actual COOP plans are restricted. Next, the Department of Conservation Resources - Lake Merriweather file contains correspondence from Joseph H. Maroon, Director of the Department of Conservation Resources, to Col. Yvonne J. Prettyman-Beck, District Engineer, U. S. Army Corps of Engineers, enclosing a draft of the project cooperation agreement between the Department of the Army and the Commonwealth of Virginia. The project relates to the repair & upgrade of the dam & appurtenant feature at Lake Merriweather. This series also contains various presentations by Secretary Whitt Clement on the Commission on the Revision of Virginia's Tax Code Transportation Subcommittee, Mark Warner's Reform Agenda Reforming VDOT, the Governor's Introduced FY 05-06 Budget & 2004 General Assembly Issues, the Report of the Secretary of Transportation Accomplishments & Initiatives, Governor Mark Warner Transportation Partnership Act to the 2005 General Assembly, Innovative Project Delivery in Virginia by the House Transportation Committee Special Subcommittee, and the Secretary of Transportation Update 2005 Transportation Initiatives by the Senate Finance Subcommittee. In addition, the series includes memorandums, correspondence, and reports regarding the Statewide Agencies Radio System program (STARS) to provide multi-channel trunked digital voice & data wireless communications that is specifically designed for public safety requirements. The Small, Women-Owned, & Minority-Owned Businesses (SWAM) file contains memorandums, reports, etc., related to the Department of Rail & Public Transportation's participation in procurement with small, women, & minority-owed firms, the Dept. of Motor Vehicles Small Business & Minority & Women-Owned Business Development Program, the Virginia Department of Transportation Supplier Diversity Program for Small, Women-Owned & Minority Businesses in response to Executive Order 29, and the Virginia Department of Aviation Small, Women-Owned, & Minority-Owned Businesses Participation Program. Lastly, the series includes the transition plans of the Virginia Information Technology Agency (VITA).
  - Continuity of Operations Plan (COOP)
    - 2004 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Department of Conservation Resources - Lake Merriweather, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Presentations, 2003-2005 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Statewide Agencies Radio System Program (STARS), 2004-2005 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Small, Women-Owned, & Minority-Owned Businesses (SWAM)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Information Technologies (VITA) Transition Plans, 2002-2004 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Series IV. Previous Administrations, 1986-2001., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 1-10)
  The Previous Administrations series is housed in ten archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order. This series contains files belonging to Secretaries of Transportation during the Gilmore, Allen, Wilder, & Baliles administrations. These files were kept by the Warner administration as reference for ongoing projects, most notably, the Commission on the Future of Transportation, the Governor's Commission of Transportation in the 21st Century, the Metropolitan Washington Airport Authority (MWAA), and the Public-Private Transportation Act Initiative (PPTA).
  The Commission on the Future of Transportation files include reports, clippings, correspondence, meeting notes, speeches, memorandums, remarks, meeting agenda, and other items related to the formation of the Commission on the Future of Transportation in Virginia in 1996. Most of the files relate to the work of Robert E. Martinez, Secretary of Transportation under Governor George Allen. The Commission on the Future of Transportation was created by an act of the General Assembly in 1996 (HJR 160 & SJR 110). The Commission was composed of twenty-five members to review the findings & recommendations of recent studies, identify major transportation needs, determine additional revenue that would be needed to finance transportation needs, and propose the means for raising & allocating such revenue.
  The Governor's Commission on Transportation in the 21st Century files contain public hearings, statements, correspondence, reports, and other items related to Phase II of Governor Gerald L. Baliles' Commission of Transportation in the 21st Century between 1986 and 1987. Phase II of the Commission focused on the role that local governments in Virginia might play in financing & controlling transportation networks.
  The Metropolitan Washington Airport Authority (MWAA) files include correspondence, statements, amendments, hearings, memorandums, clipping, and other items regarding the Washington National Airport Perimeter Rule (S 288) and the Metropolitan Washington Airports Act of 1986 Amendment (HR 1036). The MWAA was created to achieve regional control and to finance the needed improvements to facilities at Washington National & Dulles Airports. The correspondence in these files originates from Governor George Allen; Bud Shuster & Frank R. Wolf, House of Representatives; Robert E. Martinez, Secretary of Transportation; Shirley J. Ybarra, Deputy Director of Transportation; Larry Pressler, Chairman of the MWAA; and John W. Warner, Senate.
  Lastly, the Public-Private Transportation Act Initiative (PPTA) contains memorandums, presentations, proposals, agenda, correspondence, and other items regarding the Public-Private Transportation Advisory Panel's evaluation of Route 288. proposals by Tri-County Developers, FD/MK, LLC, and Virginia Transportation Constructors, LLC.
  - American Association of State Highways and Transportation Officials (AASHTO), 2000-2001. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trade, 1997-1999. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Bonds, 1997. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Bridges, 2001. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Clippings
    - 1986 (Folder 1) (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 1986 (Folder 2) (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 1986 (Folder 3) (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Commission on the Future of Transportation (HJR 160)
    - 1994-1996 Sept. 25 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 1996 Sept. 25-Nov. 25 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - 1996 Nov. 25-1997 Mar. 31 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - 1997 Mar. 31 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - 1997 Mar. 31-May 23 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - 1997 June 16-July 30 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - 1997 Aug. 1-5 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - 1997 Aug. 6-25 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - 1997 Aug. 26-Sept. 3 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - 1997 Sept. 4-Oct. 21 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - 1997 Nov. 5-Dec. 9 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - 1997 Dec. 10-19 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - 1998 Oct. 15-Dec. 15 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - 1998 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 1999 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Eight-Hour Ozone Nonattainment Designations, 1998-1999. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Enhancement Project Requests, 2001. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Commission on Transportation in the 21st Century
    - Executive Summary, 1990. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - General Information
      - 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - 1987 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Local Government Advisory Phase II
      - 1986 (Folder 1) (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - 1986 (Folder 2) (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - 1986 (Folder 3) (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - 1987 (Folder 1) (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - 1987 (Folder 2) (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - 1987 (Folder 3) (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - 1987 (Folder 4) (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - 1987 (Folder 5) (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - 1987 (Folder 6) (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - 1987 (Folder 7) (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Public Hearing
      - Pages 1-154, 1986. (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Pages 155-291, 1986. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - HOV-2, undated. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Interstate 66
    - 1977-1996 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - 1998 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Interstate 81, 1996-2001. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Interstate 895, 1996-2001. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Interstate Highway Tolls, 1998-1999. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Kings Highway Bridge, 2000-2001. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Latin America Trade & Transportation Study, 1998-2001. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Maintenance, 1997-2001. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Washington Airport Authority (MWAA)
    - 1986-1995 Feb. 28. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - 1995 Mar. 1-13. (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - 1995 Mar. 14-May. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 1995 June 16-1996 Mar. 14. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 1996 April 15-June 26. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 1996 July 1-Oct. 8. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 1996 Dec. 20-1997 Feb. 26. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Amendments, 1995. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Drafts, 1995-1996. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Hearing, 1995. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Public-Private Transportation Act Initiative (PPTA)
    - 1998 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Ferries, 1997-1999. (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Implementation Guidelines, 2001. (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Route 288
      - 1999-2000 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - 2000 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - 2000 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - 2000 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - 2000 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Maintenance Services, Inc., 1996-1998. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Revenue Ruling 63-20, 1997. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Route 17, 1995-2001. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Route 288, 1999-2001. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Transportation Coordinating Council, 1995-2000. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Transportation Proposals
    - 1991 (Folder 1) (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - 1991 (Folder 2) (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Transportation Trust Fund Allocation Formulae Study, 2001. (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - VDOT Cash Flow, 1998-1999. (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 2001-2003. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Transportation Act of 2000, 2001. (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Series V. Projects & Studies, 2000-2006., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 1-8)
  The Projects & Studies series is housed in eight archival boxes and is arranged in seven subseries. Subseries have been designated for Aviation, the Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV), the Department of Rail & Public Transportation (DRPT), Highways, the Virginia Department of Transportation (VDOT), and the Virginia Port Authority (VPA). This series represents special projects and studies adopt by the Secretary of Transportation during the administration of Governor Warner. The majority of materials can be found in the Virginia Department of Transportation subseries.
  - Subseries A: Aviation, 2000-2006., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1)
    The Aviation subseries is housed in one archival box and is arranged in alphabetical order. This subseries contains correspondence, memorandums, agency hiring requests, and other records related to the Department of Aviation and the Aviation World's Fair of 2003 at the Newport News-Williamsburg International Airport.
    - Aircraft Use Policy & Guidelines, 2005. (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Aviation World's Fair
      - 2000-2002. (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - 2002. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Aviation
      - 2002-2004. (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Agency Hiring Requests, 2002. (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Direct Aviation Tax Assessment, 2002. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Airways Loan Guarantee, 2002. (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Aviation Security Advisory, 2002. (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV), 2002-2005., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 1-2)
    The Department of Motor Vehicles subseries is housed in two archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order. This subseries contains memorandums, correspondence, legislation, decision briefs, agency hiring requests, and other items concerning the DUI Task Force, Fuel Tax Program, Hurricane Isabel, and other subjects.
    - 2002. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - 2003. (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - 2004. (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - 2005. (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Agency Hiring Requests
      - 2002-2003. (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - 2004 Jan.-July. (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - 2004 Aug.-2005 May. (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - 2005 June-Dec.. (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts Audit, 2003. (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - DUI Task Force, 2002-2004. (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Fee Report, 2003. (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Fuels Tax Program, 2004. (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Task Force to Combat Driving Under the Influence of Drugs & Alcohol, 2002-2004. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Hurricane Isabel, 2003. (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Legal Presence Legislation, 2003-2004. (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Motor Carrier Safety Improvement Act, 2005. (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Motor Vehicle Dealer Board, 2005. (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - National Guard License Plates, 2005. (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Traffic Safety Records System, 2005. (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Weigh Station Consolidation, 2002. (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Department of Rail & Public Transportation (DRPT), 2002-2006., Extent: 1 box. (Box 1)